Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/loczaki (LinkedIn) loczaki-design.framer.website/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

User Interface Design Interaction Design FigJam

Publications

My website

Loc Nguyen

UI/UX Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Interface Designer has skills in Figma, Adobe Premier, Adobe After Effects, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Audition, MS Office, Communication, English, and Leadership. Strong arts and design professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Graphic Design from FPT HCM University.

Experience

FPT Information System
User Interface Designer
January 2023 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Utop UI/UX Designer November 2022 - Present (2 years 5 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Freelance Graphic Designer August 2022 - Present (2 years 8 months)

FPT Software
UI/UX Designer
November 2022 - January 2023 (3 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Gannha
UI/UX Designer
August 2021 - August 2022 (1 year 1 month)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

FPT University

Bachelor's degree, Graphic Design · (2018 - 2022)